A very good morning friends only with varana with aana aam baat with another sheet question
viewer welcome you to the tan tandav a
this question within there strike in
question of the three most question love you
to time to answer all the question answer 10
question and after that you are the
new only question for this you can
win exciting prizes by
participating in adhin na even been
requesting you to family members
participated in the song and subscribe
point is the richest of all
of you to one leg mod in one
price you can participate in which
questions and you can win prize system
and not avid of every monday subscribe
and screen ki ki aisi ki
u all my screen ki
question a you are driving me new note
before android that choke hanging piece
of tay ko date rotating bea of ​​date you
will  Love you all ignore the game on lower your window
and question the person has real bank
his real hangouts to indicate and
replica your headlights to indicate Suraj
which is Every Day in Hindi today value and
urine this note subscribe this side I
noticed that the rider on your side
and his bottom cloth is anything I
mean first scarf made from bushes it could be scarf
or anything
now the piece of cloth that is below
his injury last one which is shooting is
also taken is going near it
so what will you do at that time ignore those people
Nuwan you ignore them and you will go away
Lallu that your window and questioned him
you will lower your window
and you will tell them that brother you have a
problem please fix it or
continuously heart to indicate you who will blow
its horn that they will wait for that
late evening Singh and you fix it
click here here rights to indicate you will
click on your headlines and indicate
that  Ram, if this is a problem then search
with us and share your tears and
tell us what will be your answer,
what will you do in such a situation, if
you see such a situation, especially when
we are going on a daily basis, then
we usually get to see this thing
that there are some ladies
sitting wearing sarees, so their
sarees are proper, dupatta, all these
things, the boys' dupatta is more,
whatever it is, so if you see any such
thing then I request you to
please tell them, you should give them a call, so that if there is
any accident
or any major incident, we
can save those people, so now tell me what do you say in such a situation, do you
ignore them and
you leave or you roll down your window and inform
them about something illegal,
instead of calling them,
you inform them by clicking on the airlines,
how do we do it, as
I told you all  After all, this entire
question will run till Team of Avery and
you can participate in it. You
come on a daily basis with five questions and
every 2 hours
we flash one question. You
have 2 hours to
participate and win
many exciting prizes. You can earn
in Hindi. All knowledge and skills, actually
Anirudh, you all know that the
situation is, all these questions are
related to it only. You all know what
you should do and what you should not do,
but what you do in such a situation, you have to
think about it and you
also have to think about how you can improve yourself
because you know one thing, now that is
a different thing when you
implement it and Delhi Police
takes up that thing separately, so now we would request you to
keep all these things in mind, implement them in your life
and help us in making our day safe so that
You know that the riders
who are dry
bike riders, their
conductor is very high,
if anything happens even a little bit according to
yours, then the
chances of getting hurt are very high
because even if it is fine and delicate, you are still saved,
but you will not be very risky, there are
chances of getting hurt a lot
and in such a situation if
any cloth gets stuck in the bike then the
chances of a Siddha Kabhi Mishra accident increase
and that or if you are very proud
here, then it becomes even more
dangerous because there you have to
travel in heavy vehicles etc.,
boxes etc., there is high security
cordon on the highway, there are all those things
and these things cannot be braked immediately,
so you should be very aware of things while driving, do
not wear any such things
which can make you dangerous and
you may have to face this danger, so you can see
on my screen Question School
Driving New  Notes Palan Rider is
Jahangir Piece of cloth near the rotating we you
will love you will no longer be haunted
nights to indicate what you will do
with this tell us this affair questions we
take you you have till 5 pm you
can participate so
you can subscribe in it
and you can also see your results on the
questions page and by your identity you
can do multiple questions
you can participate in every single question
and you can be a part of it
our main focus is road
safety we want that we have this whole
campaign we do all these things we
want that we can make you, your loved
ones safe our road users
we can make our day
safe so that we can reduce the
accidents that happen in India which is the curve of digit
we can make people aware and we
request you that whenever you go out on the road,
whether you  Even if you do
n't go out for a long distance, please
always take care of your safety measures. If you
drive a bike, then you must wear a helmet.
If you use a seat anywhere, then
wear it on the seat. If you are making children sit in the car, even at the
back,
now I would request you to make them sit at the back only after wearing a helmet.
It is very important for the safety of you and your loved ones.
So you should join us. MB Rabbi is a part of
the separate section. You also mean those who use it daily, who are on the road
daily, whoever
breaks their rules, that means you should
follow all these rules for yourself and not for others,
not to show off to others.
Now you have to follow your own rules because your
life is very important for you and
your loved ones too. Someone is waiting for you when you go
out, someone is waiting for you at home,
for them too. You
should use these road safety measures. By
showing off and following road safety rules,
you feel that you are looking very important and good.
Yes Fatak Sherlyn no if you
use Srishti misuse properly then maybe you will be
able to depend more and an example settings more subscribe and get it
and you can live the gift Veer
driving driving 09 2010 rotating
through love you will you subscribe that on
your side your
well wishers are doing right their
piece of cloth is below the
routing of the world this will which is rotating is
near it and what will you do at that time
ignore remove on you will ignore and go ahead
love Jain question religion you
will put your point down and you
will grand them about it that see
this is the sign so we pin which
indicates your day so by blowing the horn we will
try to indicate them that
please stop on the side and
fix your clothes or you click and
headlights to indicate or you will figure out the hair lights to
indicate them that
please stop and fix this thing
and are in everyday city  This awareness that we have
when we are driving, when we are driving here, then we should be
focused. The awareness that we have
when we use the road is very important,
it is mandatory, so always
wear such clothes which are comfortable for you, sir.
When you are driving
and that answer is, if you drive a four wheeler, then
focus becomes very important for you
on the road because it is very important for your new
parents, riders, drivers as
well, so now
always keep in mind that you should not
do anything that distracts your mind or
your body,
that your mind gets destroyed. So, for example,
you and other people put up a screen inside your class
and a video is playing, then the
chances of distraction
increase a lot and if you are driving while talking on the phone, then the
increase a lot and if you have a
companion who is
disturbing you, always keep in mind that whoever is
yours is ahead, Irfan Shaikh  The side light plays a
very important
role and sometimes children insist a lot on
sitting in the front seat but
you should avoid it because the children are
somewhat android and if they are doing something then the chances
of distraction
increase a lot, so
you should make them sit and explain to them that this note and
driving should
not distract you, now they should sit
properly in the back seat, if you
see in foreign countries in conferences, then
children are not allowed to sit in the front seat, there is a
special thing for them which we find
there in cars
and with the help of which they can protect themselves, that is, every day,
they only mean that they can protect the entire family,
they request you that whenever you go
out with your children, always make
them sit in the back seat and it is
not necessary that it is in the back seat because in India it happens that the
seat belt for the rear seat is not mandatory but for it's a
319 in love with Steve how to for
the switch off to like high sirwali
Artificial setting of the box acid
because that is for your safety, so
you should pay attention to these small things, to a
great extent this Rudraksha,
accidents on the road and we can prevent them
myself, I will once again
give you this question for the last time,
you are driving manual hotels, now holy
festival Asaf Khan episode 102 rotating
wheel of tattoo with love you all subscribe,
you notice that the
cloth on your side is hanging down near the rotating wheel,
so what will you do at that time, you will
ignore in motion or you will go out, roll down
your window and ask them, you will
tell them
about the recording, we will pintu
indicate rough bah bah bah bah bah phone switch off,
why will you indicate or you will indicate handsfree on
your life to indicate your hai light and by
clicking on the tips I will
tell them that please stop and get this
fixed, so now the question of the
day is now stream on questions and on love you have
* all times  to answer this question aa titu aa raha
va bank warm and you will join
you within next question morning request
you can participate in all questions and
love you all in one raksha na thank you so much
for being with me and some specific hindi
ans tune thank you so much for